London, United Kingdom 07917086219 rebeca.cazacu@gmail.com <u>GitHub</u> LinkedIn

## Alina Rebeca Cazacu (Rebeca)

## **MY STORY**

While working in Market Research, I've decided to expand my set of skills and I've fallen in love with programming.

I started to learn the basics using SoloLearn, FreeCodeCamp and other Youtube tutorials and soon enough, I realized that I enjoy learning about web-development, so I kept going forward.

With hard work and dedication, I managed to build my first <u>Portfolio</u> to provide a better overview of my progress with coding.

Now, my main goal is to learn more about programming and build a career as a web-developer.

#### **SKILLS**

ReactJs (Hooks), ES6, PWA, JavaScript, Bootstrap, CSS, HTML

## **Projects**

These are some interesting projects that I've built which helped me to learn the following:

#### **Expense Tracker**

• ReactJs Hooks (useState, useEffect, createContext, useReducer)

#### Recipe App

- CSS modules
- Working with RESTful APIs

## Etch-a-sketch

- DOM Event Listener
- Grid system (two-dimensional array)
- DOM manipulation

#### Shopping list

- PWA: manifest file
- Local Storage

#### Pomodoro Clock

- Working with audio files
- Timers

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## <u>UserTribe</u>, Copenhagen — Market Research Lead

November 2018 - July 2019

 Generating robust pipelines of leads for different clients, managing & coordinating teams of freelancers and optimizing the business flow

## **<u>LetsBuild</u>**, **Copenhagen** — *Marketing Coordinator*

July 2017 - November 2017

 Helping with social media posts and campaigns, developing case studies and working with Search Engine Marketing (SEM)

## **EDUCATION**

# <u>CphBusiness</u>, <u>Copenhagen</u> — Innovation and Entrepreneurship - Bachelor's Degree

2014 - 2018, Copenhagen

Principal subjects covered:

- Innovation & Entrepreneurship
- Marketing and Sales
- Business administration
- Project Management

## **REFERENCES**

## Ms. Victoria Berth Lyhne — Former Head of Business Insights at UserTribe

"In Business Insights we work on several projects at once and the pace is high. It is therefore important to maintain an overview and plan ahead; a capability Rebeca has demonstrated to perfection.

With her detail-oriented nature, Rebeca has been an integrated part of the success of our projects and contributed to the strengthening and stabilizing of our department and culture.

Rebeca has, despite her young age, shown an impressive level of maturity, which is exemplified by her constant care and interest in growing and contributing to the company.

Rebeca is a loyal and committed team player who will rise to the challenge and go the extra mile. It is my pleasure to recommend Rebeca to join your team and company."